Slowly.
慢慢地。
Hold your horses.
稍安毋躁。
Why did you save me?
你为什么要救我？
Why did you follow me in the past three days?
这三天你为什么关注我？
Red flowers blossoming in the south.
红色的花朵在南方盛开。
Miss Chao Nan brought tea.
朝南小姐送来了茶。
No tea, no wine.
没有茶，没有酒。
And sing the folk songs there.
并在那里唱民歌。
You know who I am now?
你现在知道我是谁了吗？
I don't know who you are.
我不知道你是谁。
But I know that
但我知道
the organization hasn't forgotten me.
组织没有忘记我。
I'm finally waking up.
我终于醒了。
Is it because
是不是因为
I've been lurking in Shanghai for over a year!
我在上海潜伏了一年多了！
Before they awaken me,
在他们叫醒我之前，
they must observe me secretly
他们必须暗中观察我
to check on me
检查我
to see if I colluded with the enemy
看看我是否与敌人勾结
and if my ability
如果我的能力
and my ability.
和我的能力。
Right?
正确的？
By the way, I have a question.
顺便说一句，我有一个问题。
That's the coffee suit just now.
这就是刚才的咖啡服。
It's closest
是最近的
and the most dangerous.
并且是最危险的。
Why did you shoot the plaid pants?
为什么要拍格子裤？
Newspaper. Newspaper.
报纸。报纸。
Selling news.
卖新闻。
The coffee suit
咖啡套装
with the Browning Pistol.
与勃朗宁手枪。
With seven shots,
经过七次射击，
the gunshot was slightly stuffy
枪声有点闷
but I heard seven gunshots
但我听到七声枪响
so the pistol
所以手枪
without bullets
没有子弹
checked pants
格子裤
his hand was a revolver M1917.
他的手是一把M1917左轮手枪。
It has six rounds,
共有六轮，
but he fired three rounds.
但他还是开了三枪。
So his pistol
所以他的手枪
with 3 rounds left.
还剩3轮。
Black top hat.
黑色高顶礼帽。
With the Soviet Union's TT33 pistol
配苏联的TT33手枪
It has eight rounds loaded.
它已装载八发子弹。
Loud sound.
声音很大。
I heard seven gunshots
我听到七声枪响
that means he had one round left
这意味着他还剩一轮
I can only save this bullet
我只能救这颗子弹
to checked pants
格子裤
but if I don't have
但如果我没有
what if I don't have a magazine?
如果我没有杂志怎么办？
I bet you do have a magazine.
我打赌你一定有一本杂志。
You're gambling on your life.
你这是在拿自己的生命做赌注。
At least I won.
至少我赢了。
Alright. Four of clubs.
好吧。四家具乐部。
Follow the Shanghai traffic line
遵循上海交通线
as instructed by Comrade Sparrow.
按照斯帕罗同志的指示。
You are officially woke up.
你正式醒来了。
From now on, I'll be your contact.
从现在开始，我就是你的联系人。
You can call me Lao Lu.
你可以叫我老鲁。
Old Lu.
老卢。
Stay here and recover.
留在这里并康复。
The clinic
诊所
Is run by my friend from French Concession.
是我法租界朋友经营的。
I woke you up urgently
我紧急叫醒你
because our organization received information
因为我们的组织收到了信息
we have a traitor.
我们有一个叛徒。
To be taken to Shanghai.
准备送往上海。
Traitor.
叛徒。
Who is this traitor?
这个叛徒是谁？
No one knows
没人知道
It's not clear who is escorting him.
目前尚不清楚谁在护送他。
According to the specific message,
根据具体消息，
they will take Train 514 tomorrow
他们明天将乘坐514次火车
from Nanjing to Shanghai.
从南京到上海。
They'll arrive at the station at about three p.m. tomorrow.
他们将于明天下午三点左右到达车站。
Zhao An of Taihe Trading Firm
Zhao An of Taihe Trading Firm
from Taihe Trading Firm.
来自泰和贸易公司。
Zhao An has a secret letter
赵安有一封密信
from a traitor.
来自叛徒。
The traitor will do great harm.
叛徒将会造成很大的伤害。
Many of our comrades who spy in the police station
我们很多在警察局做间谍的同志
might be found by him
可能会被他发现
so your mission is
所以你的任务是
find the traitor
找到叛徒
and eliminate traitors in the organization.
并消灭组织中的叛徒。
Yes
是的
the difficulties will be great
困难会很大
find a way to overcome it.
找到克服它的方法。
And look for clues as much as possible.
并尽可能地寻找线索。
You can deal with it in an emergency.
紧急情况下你可以处理它。
At the same time, you should be ready to evacuate.
同时，您应该做好撤离的准备。
If your identity is exposed,
如果你的身份暴露了
you should leave the firm and Shanghai immediately.
你应该立即离开公司和上海。
My usual
我平时的
I promise to complete the task.
我保证完成任务。
The Yumo Calligraphy and Painting Shop on Dongpushi Road.
东璞石路上的玉墨书画店。
This is where we should be contacting later.
这是我们稍后联系的地方。
This is where we'll be contacting in the future.
这是我们以后联系的地方。
Come on, Jiaping.
加油，嘉平。
Come on
快点
look at this painting.
看看这幅画。
Please write a note for me.
请帮我写一张便条。
Eat while it's hot.
趁热吃吧。
My paintings and your writing
我的画和你的文字
so a perfect match in Shanghai
所以在上海真是绝配
no one can find another in Shanghai
在上海没人能找到另一个
old Luo,
old Luo,
why are you still in the mood for painting?
为什么还有心情画画？
Do you know that Zhao An
你知道赵安吗
zhao An has a meeting today?
赵安今天有会议吗？
Don't blame me for this
不要为此责怪我
do you think I'm straightforward?
你觉得我很直率吗？
Now everyone in the business
现在每个人都在做生意
are saying that you are just a fake brand.
说你只是一个假品牌。
Zhao An is the real boss of the business.
赵安才是这家企业真正的老板。
That's enough.
这就够了。
But look at this.
但看看这个。
The Japanese only call you Zhao An at meetings.
日本人开会的时候只叫你“赵安”。
This is so not fair.
这太不公平了。
Jiaping,
Jiaping,
take a look at the painting for me.
帮我看一下这幅画。
Please comment.
请给出意见。
Alright.
好吧。
And light energy,
还有光能，
contains the power.
包含着力量。
From within.
从内部。
Brother,
兄弟，
It's time to accumulate wealth.
是时候积累财富了。
You know me.
你了解我。
Certainly.
当然。
You're my eldest brother, right?
你是我的大哥，对吧？
I'm not like those pushers who
我不像那些推手
they all went to Zhao An.
他们都去了赵安那里。
I'm determined to follow you.
我决心追随你。
Do you think that
你认为
I will deal with Zhao An sooner or later?
我迟早要对付赵安？
Not necessarily.
不必要。
I just think
我只是想
If I'm with Zhao An,
如果我和赵安在一起
wouldn't I be able to use
我不能使用
my good handwriting.
我的一手好字。
You
你
the power of this painting
这幅画的力量
a bird is out of the wood.
一只鸟从树林里飞出来。
Write cursive characters in a vigorous and nimble style
草书刚健、灵动
also,
还，
If you open the curtains,
如果你拉开窗帘，
It's bright
天很亮
chief Chen
陈科长
what are you up to?
你要做什么？
I'm sweating.
我出汗了。
It's too hot to clean up the office.
太热了，没法打扫办公室。
Let it out.
说出来。
He's busy.
他很忙。
I'll get something back.
我会拿回一些东西。
Got to go.
要走了。
Based on all information,
根据所有信息，
we can now confirm that
我们现在可以确认
the traitor Fang Hong Nan was escorted by
叛徒方洪南被押解
from Nanjing to Shanghai.
从南京到上海。
As long as we find the Martial Master and his men
只要找到武师和他的手下
and find out the traitor's southpaw
找出叛徒的左撇子
we can target him and find an opportunity to eliminate traitors.
我们可以针对他，找机会消灭叛徒。
But there was an accident.
但发生了意外。
Zhao An will take men to guard the train station.
赵安会带人去守火车站。
It would cause unpredictable difficulties and dangers
将会带来难以预料的困难和危险
to the operation.
到操作。
What should I do?
我应该怎么办？
To go or not?
去还是不去？
It's too late to report to the organization now.
现在向组织汇报已经太晚了。
We must make a decision immediately.
我们必须立即做出决定。
Watch your step.
小心台阶。
Get out of the way.
走开。
Please make way.
请让路。
I made some business.
我做了一些生意。
I agreed to meet him at the railway station.
我同意在火车站接他。
But Zhao An found out.
但赵安却发现了。
The Japanese
日本
has been very strict recently.
最近管得很严。
And Zhao An is the underling of the Japanese.
而赵安则是日本人的手下。
So he used you as his cover.
所以他用你作为他的掩护。
That's it?
就是这样？
What about you?
你呢？
What about me?
关于我的什么？
When I asked for your help,
当我向你寻求帮助时，
you reacted so quickly.
你反应这么快。
That there is something
有东西
to hide something on purpose.
故意隐藏某事。
Did you also use me to give you a cover?
你也是利用我给你打掩护吗？
I thought they wanted to catch me.
我以为他们想抓住我。
Why?
为什么？
I participated in an activity
我参加了一个活动
I participated in an activity against Wang puppet government.
我参加了反对汪伪政府的活动。
That's not like you.
那不像你。
When I was a traitor.
当我是叛徒的时候。
By the way,
顺便一提，
how come I didn't notice
我怎么没注意到
your memory is so good.
你的记忆力真好。
When Zhao An caught up with us,
当赵安追上我们时，
I told you once.
我告诉过你一次。
Remember all the information
记住所有信息
about the firm,
关于公司，
you're not bad, right?
你不坏吧？
Exactly the same.
一模一样。
I'm the chief of the General Services Section.
我是总务科科长。
But I'm good at that
但我很擅长这个
I'm in the accounting office,
我在会计室，
and I'm good at remembering these things.
我很擅长记住这些事情。
I'm not good at remembering
我不擅长记住
not only these trivial matters.
不仅仅是这些琐事。
I know.
我知道。
You have a lot of things to ask me.
你有很多事情要问我。
Go ahead then.
那就继续吧。
Why you didn't come that day.
那天你怎么没来。
We already investigated.
我们已经调查过了。
Luo Guanqun is really something.
罗冠群真是个东西。
The so-called Taihe Trading Firm
所谓的太和商行
the so-called Taihe Firm.
也就是所谓的太和商行。
The Imperial Bodyguard
帝国侍卫
Is an intelligence station
是一个情报站
under the control of Japan's Military Police Headquarters.
隶属日本宪兵司令部管辖。
We can infiltrate our enemies
我们可以渗透到敌人的内部
we can infiltrate our enemies, right?
我们可以渗透到敌人的内部，对吗？
That's right.
这是正确的。
However,
然而，
have you thought it over?
你想好了吗？
Yes, I have.
是的，我有。
I'm a Party member.
我是一名党员。
I want to do my best
我想尽力而为
to resist Japan and save the country
抗日救国
and national liberation.
和民族解放。
Once you execute a lurking mission,
一旦你执行了潜伏任务，
your identity should be more concealed.
你的身份应该更加隐蔽。
Please rest assured.
请放心吧。
I will definitely be able to do it.
我一定能做到。
I remember that
我记得那个
to marry Zuo Shuangtao before.
to marry Zuo Shuangtao before.
But you weren't there on the day of the registration.
但报名那天你不在场。
She must be very sad.
她一定很伤心吧。
How do you plan to
你打算如何
with Zuo Shuangtao?
with Zuo Shuangtao?
I...
我...
I owe her so much.
我欠她太多了。
Pay it back next life.
下辈子还吧。
Answer me. ??? I fell in love with her. ???
回答我。??? 我爱上了她。???
Why didn't you come that day?
那天你怎么没来？
I don't know.
我不知道。
I thought
我想
I can't give you
我不能给你
happy life.
幸福生活。
So you ran away?
所以你逃跑了？
Come to Shanghai
来上海吧
to be a traitor.
成为叛徒。
I only knew Luo Guanqun by chance.
我认识罗冠群只是偶然。
I didn't know he was working for the Japanese.
我不知道他为日本人工作。
It was too late when I found out.
当我发现时已经太晚了。
In addition,
此外，
just make a living.
只是谋生。
You were not like this.
你本来不是这样的。
Yes
是的
It was...
它是...
In the past.
在过去。
I was stupid in the past.
以前的我很傻。
Too childish
太幼稚了
and unrealistic.
和不现实的。
Including being with me.
包括和我在一起。
Did you come to Nanjing to find me later?
你后来来南京找我吗？
Bill, please.
结账。
Have you finished?
你完成了吗？
What about the girl who always comes with you?
那个一直陪着你的女孩呢？
Recently,
最近，
that girl always came alone
那个女孩总是一个人来
and today you're again alone?
今天你又孤身一人了吗？
Boss.
老板。
Can you do me a favor?
你可以帮我个忙吗？
What help?
有什么帮助？
That girl of yours
你的那个女孩
If I come again next time,
如果下次再来的话
can the soup be less salty?
汤可以少咸一点吗？
Use less Kaiyang.
Use less Kaiyang.
In fact, she doesn't want to trouble you.
其实她不想给你添麻烦。
She's too shy to say it.
她太害羞了，不敢说。
Alright.
好吧。
Please don't tell her.
请不要告诉她。
That I told you this?
我告诉过你这个吗？
Answer me!
回答我！
Did you come to Nanjing to find me later?
你后来来南京找我吗？
Not really.
并不真地。
Can I leave now?
我现在可以离开吗？
Not yet.
还没有。
(Sorry.)
（对不起。）
This drama won't end
这部剧不会结束
the play won't end.
戏不会结束。
I accompany you
我陪你
I'll go to the Yu Residence with you.
我和你一起去御府吧。
We need to make them believe
我们需要让他们相信
that we're couple.
我们是情侣。
Why should I listen to you?
我为什么要听你的？
Go back first
先回去吧
pick me up tomorrow morning.
明天早上来接我。
Let me leave just after taking a shower?
让我洗完澡就走？
Where should I go?
我应该去哪儿？
To your home.
到你家。
Wherever you are,
无论你在哪，
where will be my home?
哪里将是我的家？
I won't go back.
我不会回去。
Stop it.
停下来。
To let your colleagues know about this.
让你的同事知道这件事。
Then give me a kiss.
然后给我一个吻。
Before I leave.
在我离开前。
How annoying.
真烦人。
You don't want to kiss me?
你不想吻我吗？
Let me kiss you.
让我吻你。
I'm leaving now.
现在我要走了。
Sir, are you looking for me?
先生，您在找我吗？
Tonight,
今晚，
bring your people
带上你的人
to Ci'an Hospital to set up an ambush.
到慈安医院埋伏。
Yes
是的
sir, I've heard
先生，我听说
commander Shanxia is already dead.
山下司令已经死了。
Then what's the purpose of the guard at the hospital?
那么医院的门卫到底有什么目的呢？
I see.
我懂了。
If the Chinese Communist has surrendered to us,
如果中共向我们投降，
Is in the hospital now.
现在在医院。
Have you ever heard of four of clubs?
你听说过四家具乐部吗？
Four of clubs
俱乐部四
Is the mole in your firm.
是你们公司的内奸吗？
There's a Communist Party of China named Four of Clubs lurking in the background.
背后潜伏着一个名为“梅花四”的中国共产党。
Communist Party of China?
中国共产党？
Who do you think
你认为是谁
of Four Clubs?
四大俱乐部？
It's me.
这就是我。
I see
我懂了
slowly.
慢慢地。
Did you hear anything?
你听到什么了吗？
What sound?
什么声音？
Don't scare us.
别吓唬我们。
The morgue is full of dead bodies.
太平间里堆满了尸体。
With a dead body in the morgue?
太平间里有一具尸体？
I really heard that.
我确实听到了。
You must have misheard it.
你肯定听错了。
Come on. Let's go.
快点。我们走吧。
Little Liu.
小刘.
The patient at bed 307 passed away.
307床位的病人去世了。
Bring her to the morgue.
带她去太平间。
Alright.
好吧。
What the hell!
我勒个去！
Can't we even sleep now?
我们现在还不能睡觉吗？
Come on.
快点。
Don't move.
别动。
What's up
这是怎么回事
she is the number 11.
她是11号。
You remember that I put it in.
你记得我把它放进去的。
Didn't you remember it?
你不记得了吗？
Maybe I forgot.
也许我忘记了。
It must have slipped my mind.
我一定是忘记了。
Come on.
快点。
You know what?
你知道吗？
I'm the most
我是最
most meticulous person.
最细心的人。
To plug in all the plugs in.
要把所有的插头都插上。
Then tell me
然后告诉我
why was the latch on the morgue cabinet
为什么太平间柜子上有闩锁
Is open?
开了？
It's scary.
太可怕了。
Yes, it is.
是的。
Bring me to the morgue.
带我去太平间。
Who are you?
你是谁？
Come on.
快点。
This way, please.
这边请。
The traitor Fang Hong Nan has arrived in Shanghai.
汉奸方洪南已抵达上海。
Why is he suddenly so quiet?
他怎么突然这么安静了？
Such an important person
这么重要的一个人
could've caused huge waves.
可能会引起巨大的波浪。
But they don't show any sign to take any action.
但他们没有表现出采取任何行动的迹象。
Could she be
她会不会是
when Shanxia was assassinated at the railway station,
当山霞在火车站被刺杀时，
fang Hongnan was also injured.
方宏南也受伤了。
I heard that the guards under the mountain were injured.
听说山下的侍卫受伤了。
To hide his identity,
为了隐藏自己的身份，
and framed Fang Hongnan as a guard?
还陷害方洪南当护卫？
Among the injured victims who checked in today,
在今天报到的受伤受害者中，
Is still no left-handed.
依然没有左撇子。
Would it be that Fang Hongnan was seriously injured and died?
难道方洪南重伤身亡？
Try to think again.
尝试再想一想。
Try to think about it.
试着想一想。
Anything abnormal tonight?
今晚有什么异常吗？
Hearing your words,
听到你的话，
I remember that.
我记得那个。
I saw the back of a male doctor.
我看到了一个男医生的背影。
But the doctors on duty tonight
但今晚值班的医生
on duty tonight
今晚值班
but there are no male doctors.
但没有男医生。
That man
那个人
Is pretending to be the male doctor.
冒充男医生。
Stand up.
起来。
That's the way I saw his back.
我就是这样看到他的背影的。
He must want to run away.
他一定是想逃走。
But he fell to his death.
但他却摔死了。
Let's see who she is.
让我们看看她是谁。
Aren't these the bodies in Counter No.2?
这不是2号柜台的尸体吗？
Let's see who it is
让我们看看是谁
section Chief Chen, Miss Zuo
陈科长、左小姐
get in the car
上车
old Luo asked you to come?
老罗叫你来？
It's not like you don't know
你又不是不知道
you know that.
你懂的。
When I heard that Ms. Zuo is the niece of the Yu family,
当听说左女士是于家的侄女时，
when you hear that Miss Zuo is the niece.
当你听说左小姐是侄女时。
Forget about it.
忘掉它。
We still have to do some shopping in the mall.
我们还得去商场买点东西。
No need.
不需要。
They've got all the gifts.
他们已经得到了所有的礼物。
Come on.
快点。
It's very considerate of me.
真是太为我着想了。
Shuangtao, it's really you.
双桃，真的是你。
Look at this.
看这个。
You've changed so much.
你改变了很多。
Come on, aunt.
来吧，阿姨。
We haven't seen each other for years.
我们已经很多年没有见面了。
You look younger every day.
你看起来一天比一天年轻。
Not really.
并不真地。
I'm already old.
我已经老了。
Mrs. Yu doesn't know she's not aged.
于夫人不知道自己还没有老。
She should be in her early thirties at most.
她最多应该三十岁出头。
He's a man of striking appearance.
他是一个外表引人注目的男人。
Such a sweet young man like him.
像他这样可爱的年轻人。
Yes
是的
jiaping,
jiaping,
you mentioned it in the letter.
你在信中提到了这一点。
Hi, Mrs. Yu.
嗨，于女士。
So you're Jia Ping?
So you're Jia Ping?
You finally see your natural face today.
今天你终于看到了你本来的面容。
Go there.
去那里。
Every letter of Shuangtao mentions you.
双桃的每一封信都提到你。
But in recent years,
但近年来，
he didn't mention it much this year.
今年他没怎么提这件事。
I thought...
我想...
Sorry.
对不起。
Look at my mouth.
看看我的嘴。
Oh, right.
啊对。
Why did you come to Shanghai
你为什么来上海
without telling me?
不告诉我？
I wrote you a letter.
我给你写了一封信。
You didn't receive it?
你没有收到吗？
No, I didn't.
不，我没有。
A month ago.
一个月前。
It's alright.
没关系。
We're all here now.
我们现在都在这里。
This is the most important thing.
这是最重要的。
It doesn't matter if I receive this letter.
我是否收到这封信并不重要。
In this age,
在这个时代，
everything is in chaos.
一切都处于混乱之中。
It became a mess.
事情变得一团糟。
And got lost.
然后迷路了。
They are normal.
他们很正常。
Normal.
普通的。
Standing here and talking for so long,
站在这里聊了这么久
go in and talk.
进去说话。
Go in.
进去。
Mrs. Yu, I won't go in there.
于太太，我不进去。
I've completed my task
我已经完成了我的任务
that's it.
就是这样。
Thank you for your hard work.
感谢你的努力工作。
Goodbye, Mrs. Yu.
再见，于女士。
-Bye. -See you.
-再见。-再见。
This way, please.
这边请。
You have become
你已经成为
have become more beautiful.
变得更加美丽了。
What?
什么？
Drive slowly.
慢速行驶。
Is this Jiaping?
这是家平吗？
You don't know.
你不知道。
Our Zheng family was once
我们郑家曾经
we were all from wealthy families.
我们都来自富裕家庭。
Within tens of miles,
方圆数十里之内，
within a radius.
半径内。
Guoguo once mentioned this before.
果果之前也曾提到过这一点。
My mother told me that
我妈妈告诉我
she was thin and weak as a child
她小时候又瘦又弱
and was bullied a lot.
并被欺负很多。
And you protected her.
而你保护了她。
So many brothers and sisters.
这么多兄弟姐妹。
Your mom and I are the closest.
我和你妈妈是最亲近的。
Don't mention it.
别提了。
Whenever I mention your mother,
每当我提到你妈妈
whenever I mention your mom.
每当我提到你妈妈。
Guoguo, now that you're in Shanghai
果果，你现在在上海了
you're here,
你在这里，
my aunt's house is your home.
我姨妈家就是你的家。
You can live here.
你可以住在这里。
You can tell her whatever she needs
你可以告诉她她需要什么
you always told her
你总是告诉她
to take it easy.
放轻松。
Do you know
你知道吗
by the way, there's work.
顺便说一句，还有工作。
Don't worry.
不用担心。
And don't worry.
别担心。
I'll tell your uncle
我会告诉你叔叔
and ask him to
并要求他
and take care of it.
并照顾好它。
Search carefully.
仔细寻找。
Must be happy
一定要幸福
with your husband.
和你的丈夫。
It's getting late.
天色已晚。
I have to prepare lunch.
我必须准备午餐。
I'll cook a few dishes
我会煮几个菜
to welcome you.
欢迎您。
Mrs. Yu is beautiful and kind.
于夫人美丽又善良。
You can cook too.
你也可以做饭。
It's great honor
这是莫大的荣幸
to marry you.
嫁给你。
Guoguo.
Guoguo.
A handsome man like Jiaping
A handsome man like Jiaping
young people like him
像他这样的年轻人
should have been brought to your aunt long ago.
早就应该带给你姨妈了。
You guys chat.
你们聊天吧
You guys have a chat.
你们聊聊吧
Xiaoli, come with me.
小丽，跟我来吧。
Alright.
好吧。
Mrs. Yu mentioned the letter just now.
刚才余夫人提到了那封信。
Big Scoop is suspecting.
大勺怀疑。
What can we do
我们可以做什么
how about this?
这个怎么样？
You can write more letters
你可以写更多的信
within one year.
一年内。
And different periods.
而且不同时期。
Using papers from different periods
使用不同时期的论文
and pens.
和笔。
I can leave the postmark
我可以留下邮戳
I will find a way.
我会找到办法的。
I'm going to work in the business.
我要去企业工作。
You're so meticulous.
你真是太细心了
To be a traitor.
成为叛徒。
What a pity
真可惜
chief Chen
陈科长
what took you so long?
你怎么这么久？
For you to come.
为了你的到来。
Waiting for me?
正在等我？
What is it?
它是什么？
By order of Chief Kimura,
奉木村长官之命，
all employees of the firm
公司全体员工
to the grove behind the building.
到建筑物后面的小树林。
I don't know
我不知道
I don't know either
我也不知道
It's very likely that
很有可能的是
nothing good.
没什么好的。
Come on.
快点。
This is the horse Zhao An gave to Mucun.
这是赵安送给木村的马。
It was said to be transported from Manchuria.
据说是从满洲运来的。
From Central Asia.
来自中亚。
Look at that.
看那个。
What does it mean?
这是什么意思？
You asked us here to watch others hang?
你让我们来这里看别人被吊死？
I'm afraid we're not watching others being hanged,
恐怕我们不会看着别人被绞死
rather, one of us will be hanged!
相反，我们中的一个人会被绞死！
Have you heard who is going to be hanged?
你听说过谁将被绞死吗？
No one.
没有人。
Is everyone here?
大家都在吗？
Everyone is here.
每个人都在这里。
Everyone,
每个人，
although Taihe Trading Firm
虽然泰和商行
Is a trading company,
是一家贸易公司，
you know who we work for
你知道我们为谁工作
what we do
我们所做的
we all know that
我们都知道
that some anti-Japanese elements
一些反日分子
tried to sneak in
试图潜入
to steal intelligence
窃取情报
and sabotage the China-Japan friendship,
破坏中日友好，
to bring common prosperity to East Asia.
实现东亚共同繁荣。
Today
今天
we gathered here
我们聚集在这里
because we have definite information.
因为我们有明确的信息。
There's a spy
有间谍
In the firm
在公司里
under the cover of four of clubs.
在四家具乐部的掩护下。
Today
今天
we're going to show a ghost
我们要展示一个幽灵
kill the four of clubs.
杀死梅花四人。
I'm afraid you don't know
恐怕你不知道
under threat from
受到威胁
by the Great Japanese Empire and the peaceful government,
由大日本帝国和和平政府，
a CPC defector came here
一名中共叛逃者来到这里
he identified four of clubs.
他指出了其中的四支球杆。
Officer Mu Cun,
木村警官，
now show us the traitor.
现在让我们看看叛徒。
Come on out!
快出来吧！
Fang Hongnan,
Fang Hongnan,
all the people in the commercial are here.
广告里的所有人都在这里。
Everyone in the business is here.
业内人士都在这里。
You have to make sure
你必须确保
look at them.
看他们。
Check out
查看
see if there are any Chinese Communists.
看看有没有中国共产党。
Chief Kimura.
木村队长。
I need to confirm one by one.
我需要一一确认。
How about this?
这个怎么样？
If he's not someone,
如果他不是一个人，
I'll pat his shoulder.
我会拍拍他的肩膀。
The sleeve and button of his left hand
左手的袖子和纽扣
Is much worse than that of his right hand
比他的右手差很多
It shows that he wrote with his left hand.
可见他是用左手写字的。
It's the same as my previous judgment.
和我之前的判断是一样的。
Is that Fang Hongnan?
那是方洪南吗？
This person?
这个人？
I am an unmarried accountant.
我是一名未婚会计师。
I'm sure you've never seen me before.
我确信你以前从未见过我。
I'm Luo Guanqun's.
I'm Luo Guanqun's.
I'm the manager's wife.
我是经理的妻子。
How could it be me?
怎么会是我呢？
Alright.
好吧。
Kimura must be looking for
木村一定在找
the secret letter under the mountain.
山下密信。
If he gets the secret letter first,
如果他先拿到密信的话
It would be over.
一切都会结束了。
But there was no letter on the body in the hospital.
但医院里的尸体上却没有任何信件。
Instead of just sitting here,
而不是坐在这里，
you'd better go to the commercial firm and investigate
你最好去商业公司调查一下
Mr. Fang,
Mr. Fang,
I am just a guard.
我只是一名警卫。
Sir, there's no one in the business.
先生，这行没人。
I'm going to the door.
我要去门口了。
Mr. Fang,
Mr. Fang,
look carefully.
仔细地看。
Don't get the wrong person.
别找错人了。
You would be four of clubs.
你们将成为梅花四人。
I once saw you
我曾经见过你
a Communist Party meeting.
共产党会议。
Fang Hongnan.
Fang Hongnan.
Are you sure that
你确定吗
chen Jiaping is four of clubs.
陈家平是俱乐部的四人。
No, no, Captain Zhao.
不不不，赵队长。
Mr. Fang must have got the wrong person.
方先生一定认错人了。
Manager Luo.
Manager Luo.
Officer Kimura,
木村警官，
I've been working in the business for a long time.
我已经在这个行业工作了很长时间了。
I can't be a Communist Party spy.
我不能当共产党特务。
Mr. Luo can testify for me.
罗先生可以为我作证。
Officer Kimura.
木村警官。
Even if I was a Communist Party spy,
就算我是共产党特务，
I wouldn't choose a four of clubs
我不会选择四家具乐部
to be my code name.
成为我的代号。
With my personality,
以我的个性，
why should I choose Q or K?
为什么我应该选择Q或K？
Chen Jiaping,
Chen Jiaping,
no need to deny it.
无需否认。
I want to invite you
我想邀请你
to test my horse.
来测试我的马。
To
到
to think.
去思考。
Hello
你好
I want to see Chen Jiaping.
我想见陈家平。
I... I know you are
我...我知道你是
you're the girlfriend of Chief Chen
你是陈科长的女朋友
she's called
她叫
left Pair Tao.
留下了双涛。
That's right
这是正确的
miss Zuo, are you here to see Section Chief Chen?
左小姐，您是来看陈科长的吗？
You came at a bad time
你来得不是时候
what's up
这是怎么回事
today,
今天，
with the firm today.
今天与该公司。
Or is it something
或者是某事
chief Chen is in trouble
陈局长有麻烦了
what happened to Jiaping?
家平怎么了？
I just want to
我只想
I couldn't bear to watch it anymore.
我不忍心再看了。
So I ran back.
于是我就跑回来了。
I advise you
我劝你
go back now.
现在就回去吧。
What happened?
发生了什么？
Can you take me to see him?
你能带我去见他吗？
If you
如果你
the place,
那个地方，
let me show you.
我来给你展示。
Hurry.
匆忙。
Guoguo.
Guoguo.
Jia Ping.
Jia Ping.
Jiaping.
Jiaping.
Miss Zuo, you are here.
左小姐，你来了。
You two...
你们俩...
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Miss Zuo.
Miss Zuo.
You were also kept in the dark like us?
你也和我们一样被蒙在鼓里吗？
Your boyfriend, Chen Jia Ping
你男朋友陈家平
Is a Communist.
是一名共产党员。
That's impossible.
这不可能。
That's bullshit!
那是胡说！